go90.com 2016-03-21

# Go90 App Privacy Policy | About Verizon

  1. Home
  2. Go90 App Privacy Policy

The [go90 app](http://www.go90app.com/learn) allows you to view videos, clips, live events, images and other content; create, save and share video clips (called “cuts”); establish a profile and share your favorite cuts with friends; create groups to share content with people who have similar tastes or interests (called “crews”); follow people and crews you like; and post comments. go90’s collection and use of information is covered by the Verizon privacy policy as well as go90-specific practices described here.

Each go90 user creates a profile consisting of user name and picture (if you choose to add one). The profile will also show any cuts you create, crews you join and comments you post. Other go90 users can view profiles and may copy or share profile information associated with you outside of go90 via texting, email and sharing in other social media. You can add additional information to your profile if you choose, such as your name, and that additional information will also be publicly available. You can modify your profile including deleting your own cuts or comments.

##### Information we collect

We collect information you provide (for example, your email and age) as well as information about your device and your use of the go90 services. This includes content you view, cuts you create and share, your comments, your followers and your crews. When you allow it, go90 collects information about your device location and your contacts. go90 also collects information from your device including your mobile number, device identifiers, device type and operating system.

##### Information shared

Information we collect is used to deliver, maintain and support the go90 services; enhance application features; customize and personalize your experiences including the advertisements you see; and provide social network interactions. We may also identify you as a go90 user to other go90 users if these users give us access to their contact lists and the email address you provide at registration matches one on their contact list, but we don’t share your email address with other users. go90 information may be shared within the Verizon family of companies, including AOL.

Go90 is supported by advertisements, so most go90 features are provided without charge. We use information you provide and information collected through your use of go90 to deliver more relevant ads. We may combine this data with data from other Verizon affiliates or third-parties in deciding which ads to serve you in go90. We also may use information collected from go90 for other purposes described in the Verizon and [AOL ](http://privacy.aol.com/privacy-policy/)privacy policies. For example, we may share information that you provide, the interests you show and your uses of the app within the Verizon family of companies for relevant advertisements in the go90 app and in other places, including non-Verizon sites and services.

##### Your choices

The Verizon Privacy Policy and [AOL privacy policy](http://privacy.aol.com/) provide detailed information about choices you have with respect to the ways in which you receive advertising outside of go90. You control whether go90 may collect and use location and contact information about your device. You will provide the initial permission and you may change your choice at any time in your device settings.
